{
    "subject": "resource/The_Neighbourhood",
    "predicate": "property/genre",
    "object": "resource/Indie_rock",
    "human_readable": "The Neighbourhood is an Indie rock genre.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8570621609687805,
            "question": "Are there any specific subgenres within Indie rock that The Neighbourhood aligns with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4242672920227051,
            "question": "Has The Neighbourhood collaborated with any other musicians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4120785892009735,
            "question": "Who are the main members of The Neighbourhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3887171447277069,
            "question": "What type of music is The Neighbourhood known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36053723096847534,
            "question": "Are there any other artists that share a similar musical style with The Neighbourhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22077040374279022,
            "question": "What are some common lyrical topics explored by The Neighbourhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21396410465240479,
            "question": "Can you describe the sound of The Neighbourhood's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2113969326019287,
            "question": "What are some popular songs by The Neighbourhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1774175614118576,
            "question": "What is the overall mood or theme often found in The Neighbourhood's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0888119637966156,
            "question": "When did The Neighbourhood first gain popularity?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Neighbourhood is an Indie rock genre.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5716_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall mood or theme often found in The Neighbourhood's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5716_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular songs by The Neighbourhood?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5716_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the sound of The Neighbourhood's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5716_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5716_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5716_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5716_153.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5716_162.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5716_172.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5716_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5716_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5716_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5716_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5716_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The output should be:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}\n\nHere's why:\n\n* The documents mention The Neighbourhood as a \"band\" and \"rock and indie rock band\", which suggests that they are part of the Indie rock genre.\n* There is no information provided in the documents that contradicts this statement.\n\nTherefore, based on the context provided, it appears that the statement \"The Neighbourhood is an Indie rock genre\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context information supports that The Neighbourhood is an indie rock band. Multiple documents mention their involvement with the indie rock scene, including references to their debut album and music style."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}